翻译 NETFLIX　校对 皮带断了
特效 小布　后期&压制 Jason肖
恶魔城
第三季 第10集
在哪里
Where is it?
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
如果我得尊称你为"大人" 那我就放弃计划
If I have to call you "Sir," I am going to give up
去和那个可能会在我睡着时吃掉我的眼睛的
and live in a ghost town with a mad magician woman
发疯的女魔法师住在鬼城里
who will probably eat my eyes while I sleep.
我可能独居得太久了
I may have been on my own too long.
停止破坏 停止放火
No more destruction. No more fires.
杀光所有人 但要保住这座城
Kill the people, but leave the city standing.
传令下去
Tell the others.
也许将来会有其他人占领这座城
Perhaps others will occupy this city one day.
又或者 它会变成一处古迹
Or, perhaps, it will become a monument.
又一个死在睡梦中的
Another hopeful idea
满怀希望的想法
that died in its sleep.
多美好的夜晚啊
It's a beautiful night.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
很可能就是真正的地狱
Well, that is, very probably, actually, Hell.
你怎么知道
And how would you know that?
我和波西米亚国王相处过一个可怕的夜晚
One terrible night with the King of Bohemia
还吸食了一袋不是鸦片的东西
and a bag of something that turned out not to be opium.
真的来不及讲故事了
We really don't have time for the story.
你能关上通往地狱的门吗
Can you close that door into Hell?
不容易
Well, not easily.
但我愿意试试
But, I will try.
赛珐 你会力挺我吗
Sypha, do you have my back?
一如既往
Always.
这东西怎么还不死
How is this thing still standing?
因为它聚集着最近被杀的人的灵魂
Because it's been filled with the souls of the recently murdered.
所以 我要多杀几次才行吗
So, I'm going to have to kill it several times over?
他们还说村里的晚上没什么消遣
And they say there's nothing fun to do in villages at night.
萨拉 你这个混蛋
Sala, you fuck.
动作很快啊
You're fast.
你击败我了 好样的
You have bested me. Well done.
但你可能赢不了这场仗
But you may not win the war.
到处都是我的人
My men are everywhere.
结束了
It's over.
你已经死了
You're already dead.
放手
Let go!
萨拉
Sala.
你穿过后方的空地进入树林
Take the back field into the woods.
在小路的岔路口向右走 越过小河 直到看见一棵苹果树
Go right at the fork and over the creek until you reach the apple tree.
站在那棵树前
Stand in front of it.
你就会看到安全之路
You will see your path to safety.
为什么 为什么告诉我这个
Why? Why would you tell me this?
到头来
It turns out that you
你的判断力比我更好
were the better judge of all things.
快跑 萨拉
Run, Sala!
我撑不住了
I can't get hold of it.
该死
Damn it.
你这该死的东西
Damn you!
这一切都是为了复活该死的弗拉德·特佩斯吗
All this to bring back Vlad bloody Tepes?
所有的死亡和恐怖都是为了那个吸血鬼吗
All this death and horror for that leech?
没错 这一切
Yes. All this.
你们屠杀整个镇子
All the strength you gathered
吸食他们的灵魂 就是为了聚集力量
from murdering a town and drinking its soul.
我不能移动回廊里的窗口
I can't move the window in the corridor.
但是你能
But, you can!
现出我想看的东西 你这该死的杂种
Show me what I want to see, you fucking bastard!
他果然是魔法师
He really is a magician.
给我看
Show me!
贝尔蒙特 杀了它
Belmont! Kill it!
我要关闭回廊了
I'm closing the Corridor!
快出去
Get out now!
谢谢
Thank you!
谢谢你们两位
Thank you both!
后会有期
I'll see you again!
怎么回事
What's happening?
你一直在骗我们
You've been lying to us.
我没有
I have not.
你有
You have.
因为所有人都欺骗我们
Because everybody lies to us.
所有人都对我们有所隐瞒
Everybody hides things from us.
你不会帮我们的 因为没人会帮我们
You won't help us. Because nobody helps us.
我们会搞清楚怎么移动这座城堡
We will work out how to move this castle.
我们会弄清你所有的秘密
We will find all your secrets.
然后用它们建造自己的帝国
We will use them to build our own empire.
我把一切都给了你们
I gave you everything.
不 才没有 没人会那么做
No, you didn't. Nobody does.
半个世界的人都在欺骗我们
We have been lied to and cheated across half the world.
你指望我们会相信你不一样吗
Do you expect us to believe you're different?
我尽力了
I tried to be.
你还没教我们魔法 你不会移动城堡
You haven't taught us magic. You won't move the castle.
你和其他人没什么两样
You're just like all the others.
拜托 我知道你们吃尽了苦头
Please. I know your lives have been hard.
但并非全世界都与你们为敌
But the world is not against you.
我不与你们为敌
I am not against you.
你当然不是了
Of course you're not.
因为你已经死了
You're already dead.
我告诉过你们 我父亲不喜欢魔法武器
I told you my father didn't like magical weapons.
但我没说我没用过它们
I did not say I didn't use them.
我从没骗过你们
I never lied to you.
我杀了萨拉
I've killed Sala.
他在哪里
Where is he?
你穿过后方的空地进入树林
Take the back field into the woods.
在小路的岔路口向右走
Go right at the fork in the path.
就会找到他
You'll find him.
把我的刀给我
Find me my knife.
为什么
Why?
因为 我要在地狱等那个混蛋
Because, I'm going to wait for that bastard in hell
等他来了 我要再杀他一次
and kill him all over again when he arrives.
烧掉我的房子
Burn my house down.
他身下
What's all that
都是些什么啊
under him?
这陷阱使用得很频繁
This thing's been used a lot.
那些小骨头是什么的
What are those small bones?
动物吗
Animals?
他让我烧掉房子
He asked me to burn it down.
房子还撑得住呢
It's actually still standing.
我们该不该烧掉仅存的房屋之一呢
Should we burn down one of the few buildings left?
那是他的临终遗愿
It was his last request.
你知道吗
You know what?
进去看看吧
Let's go in.
我只想知道那扇门后面是什么
I just want to know what's behind that door.
这样不太对
That doesn't seem right.
来吧 这家伙做事井井有条
Come on. This guy was so organized.
里面也许有一些幸存者能用上的东西
There may be something the survivors could really use.
这里的每个小故事都影响巨大
Here, every little story is a huge thing.
农牧事故 疾病
A farming accident. A sickness.
迷路的孩子
A lost child.
不得不说
I have to say,
听上去管理小镇可一点也好玩
running a town does not sound like it's fun.
其中自有它的小乐趣
It has its little pleasures.
坑里的衣服碎片
The scraps of clothing in the pit.
小骨头
The small bones.
对
Yeah.
他说是他杀了萨拉
He said he killed Sala.
对
Yeah.
那是他挖的坑
It was his pit.
他是法官
He was the Judge.
他找到了自己的小乐趣
And he found his little pleasures.
我想离开这里 现在就走
I want to leave here, now,
再也不回来了
and never come back.
莫拉娜是个天才
Morana's a genius.
不过 那都是我的主意
It was all my idea, though.
-我...  -别说了 斯崔格
- I... - Leave it, Striga.
说一遍 莫拉娜是个天才
Say it. Morana's a genius.
都是我的主意
It was still my idea.
你的主意相当于
Your idea was the equivalent
一个村野白痴走进来说
of the village idiot walking in here and saying,
"我觉得我们可以通过揍一条鱼来点火"
"I think we should be able to light fires by punching a fish."
根本说不通 而莫拉娜还是做到了
It basically made no sense and Morana made it work anyway.
我的天啊
For God's sake.
斯崔格 她知道
Striga, she knows.
我当然不知道
I certainly do not.
不 你知道
Yes, you do.
你怎么可能知道
How could you know that?
我是天才
I am a genius.
你们都是天才 别争了
You're all brilliant. Stop bickering.
他来这里干什么
What's he doing here?
丽诺尔 这是我们的房间
Lenore, this is our room.
连守卫都不能进来
We don't even let the guards in here.
你们想让赫克托帮忙 所以
You wanted Hector's help. So,
赫克托偶尔可以与我们同席
Hector gets to sit with us sometimes.
接着
Catch.
这是什么
What's this?
我们这里有几位吸血鬼魔法师
Well, we have a few vampire magicians here.
我让其中一位做的
I had one of them make those.
我还借了他的书
I also borrowed that book from him.
那个铁匠魔法师 勇敢之选
The blacksmith magician. Brave choice.
圣诞期间 斯崔格差点把他放在阳光下暴晒
Striga almost had him staked out in the sunlight over Christmas
因为他熔了她的旧盔甲
after he melted down her old armor
想给自己做一双新脚
to make himself new feet.
就是他 可爱的老头 不停地抽搐
That's him, lovely old man. Strange twitch.
这是奴隶戒指
These are slave rings.
其中一个到了赫克托手上
One of them found its way on to Hector's hand
就在他发誓效忠我的时候
while he was swearing his loyalty to me.
什么
Excuse me?
是的 当时他正在我体内
Yes. He was inside me at the time.
那 你们都知道 赫克托锻造的黑暗生物
So, as you know, when Hector forges a night creature,
效忠于他
they are loyal to him.
但是现在
But now!
戒指上的咒语 把他和我绑在了一起
He is bound to me through the spell on these rings.
当他锻造的黑暗生物时 它们效忠于他
When he makes a night creature, they're loyal to him,
而他效忠于我 所以它们也效忠于我
and he swore loyalty to me, so they're loyal to me, too.
所有这些戒指都是相连的
All these rings are linked.
戴上戒指 他的黑暗生物也会效忠于你们
Wear the ring, and his night creatures will be loyal to you, too.
如果赫克托试图伤害我们 或者摘掉戒指或试图逃跑
And if Hector ever tries to harm us, or take it off, or run away,
他的戒指会引发巨痛
his ring will cause him so much pain
让他以为自己的心脏快掉出来了
that he'll think he shat out his own heart.
问题解决了
Problem solved!
我的天
Bloody hell.
作为回报 我们要改造一栋旧楼让他住进去
In return, we're going to convert one of the old outbuildings for him to live in.
一定要装饰得好看些
We're going to make it nice.
他要和我们活得一样舒服
He's going to live just as well as we do,
在城堡里自由通行
and he's going to have freedom of the castle.
我看不行
I don't think so.
我看行 他总要有所回报
I do. He gets something back from this.
他会拥有舒适的生活和安全感
He gets a comfortable life. He gets to feel safe.
-我能不能…  -莫拉娜会...
- Do I get to... - Morana will...
嘘 大人们在说话
Shush. The real people are talking.
莫拉娜会负责安排的
Morana will make the arrangements.
斯崔格组织锻造
Striga will organize the forging.
卡米拉必须同意这一切并忍气吞声
Carmilla will agree to all this and live with it.
我不是天才 她才是
I'm not a genius. She is.
这位吸血鬼姐妹一直都有自己的诡计
The vampire sister had her own scheme all along.
我的天
My God.
你收养了他
You adopted him!
卡米拉
Carmilla.
好吧 好了
All right. Fine.
他的住处需要一张很大的床
And the house will need a really big bed.
没想到他还是个性爱高手
It turns out he's actually fairly good at sex,
我想培养他
and I want to train him.
走开 真的
Get away from me. Uck, seriously.
快走开
Please leave now.
我不需要知道这个
I don't think I needed that information?
-再见  -我需要知道那个吗
- Bye-bye. - Did I need to know that?
你耍了我 把我变成了你的奴隶
You tricked me and made me your slave.
没有的事
I did no such thing.
你把我变成了奴隶
You made me a slave.
我的人生结束了
My life is over!
你的命得救了 赫克托
Your life is saved, Hector.
我给了你一直以来真正需要的东西
And I gave you what you always really needed.
我把你变成了我的宠物
I made you into my pet.
真是大错特错了
This could not have gone more wrong.
这到底是怎么了
What happened?
我们花了几个月时间过你的生活
We've spent a couple of months living your life.
充满冒险和胜利
Adventures and victories.
现在 该过我的生活了
And now, we're living my life.
好吧
Well.
我想 我应该在所有地方都竖起大牌子
I suppose I could've put up big signs all over the place.
"严禁进入 有生命危险
Do not enter. Danger of death.
放弃一切希望"
Abandon all hope.
诸如此类的
That sort of thing.
不过 对于死去的老爸来说
But this seemed to work well enough
这样似乎也够了
for dead old dad.
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠